Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 8 and District 8 Locals, 1936-1957 UE.4.1.8
ULS Archives & Special Collections
UE National Office Records Relating to District 8 and District 8 Locals
1936-1957
ULS Archives & Special Collections
United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America
UE.4.1.8
7.5 Linear Feet (7 boxes)
This series contains files on United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) District 8 and its locals collected by the UE national office. Included are correspondence, publications, minutes, and news clippings regarding local strikes, events, and organizing efforts.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Previous Citation
UE National Office Records Relating to District 8 and District 8 Locals, 1936-1957, UE.4.1.8, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Scope and Content Notes
District 8 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) originally included locals in southern Ohio, but after the United Farm Equipment and Metal Workers joined the UE in 1949, the district grew both in the number of locals and in geographic coverage to incorporate much of the Mid West. These locals are now part of the UE's Western Region. This series contains files on UE District 8 and its locals collected by the UE national office. Included are correspondence, publications, minutes, and news clippings regarding local strikes, events, and organizing efforts. Most of the correspondence is between UE national officers and district or local officers.
Arrangement
This series has been arranged into two subseries. The first contains records pertaining to District 8. The other subseries contains records pertaining to specific locals within the district, and are further arranged numerically by local number into sections.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America in 1975, 1986, 1997, and 2001.
Related Material
UE District 8 Records, 1940s-1950s, UE.15.8, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Campaign to Organize Graduate Students, UE Local 896 Records, 1990-1996, UE.16.896, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- United States -- History; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- Middle West -- History; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions -- Middle West -- History -- 20th century; Labor; Emspak, Julius; Matles, James J.; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. District 8; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America
- District 8, 1.
  - District 8 Constitution, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - District 8 Constitution, October 1942 - June 12, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - District 8 Constitution, 1942 - 1954 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - District 8 Constitution, 1950 - 1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - District 8 Officers Lists, October 1943 - January 2, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - District 8 Executive Board Meeting Minutes, June 20, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - District 8 Executive Board Meeting Minutes, January 30, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
  - District 8 Executive Board Meeting Minutes, June 26, 1943 - January 15, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - District 8 Executive Board Meeting Minutes, August 4, 1944 - August 10, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - District 8 Executive Board Meeting Minutes, November 9, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - District 8 Executive Board Meeting Minutes, January 17, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - District 8 Executive Board Meeting Minutes, July 31, 1945 - September 10, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - District 8 Executive Board Meeting Minutes, June 24, 1950 - March 1, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - District 8 Executive Board Resolutions, January 16, 1944 - December 16, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Resolution Regarding Dues, January 16, 1944; 1.
    - Resolution Regarding Veterans and UE News with July 26, 1945, William Sentner Letter to Julius Emspak, July 13, 1945; 2.
    - Resolution Regarding Marshall Plan, December 6, 1947; 3.
    - Resolution Regarding Foreign Policy, July 31, 1948; 4.
    - Resolution Regarding Wages and Housing, July 31, 1948; 5.
    - Resolution Regarding Education Publicity, July 31, 1948; 6.
    - Resolution Regarding Taxes, July 31, 1948; 7.
    - Resolution Regarding Officers and Taxes, July 31, 1948; 8.
    - Resolution Regarding Organization, July 31, 1948; 9.
    - Resolution Regarding Legislation, July 31, 1948; 10.
    - Resolution Regarding Deportation, July 31, 1948; 11.
    - Resolution Regarding Conscription, July 31, 1948; 12.
    - Resolution Regarding Political Action, July 31, 1948; 13.
    - Resolution Regarding Speed-up, July 31, 1948; 14.
    - Resolution Regarding Democratic Rights, July 31, 1948; 15.
    - Resolution Regarding Company Spies, July 31, 1948; 16.
    - Resolution Regarding Thomas Committee, July 31, 1948; 17.
    - Resolution Regarding Strikes and UE News, July 31, 1948; 18.
    - Resolution Regarding Minimum Contract Standards, July 31, 1948; 19.
    - Resolution Regarding Racism and Veterans, July 31, 1948; 20.
    - Resolution Regarding Farmers, July 31, 1948; 21.
    - Resolution Regarding Defense Committee, December 16, 1950; 22.
    - Resolution Regarding Wages, December 16, 1950; 23.
  - District 8 Council Meeting Minutes, August 8, 1937 - September 24, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - District 8 Council Meeting Minutes, March 30 - September 21, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - District 8 Council Meeting Minutes, March 15, 1941 - March 29, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - District 8 Council Meeting Minutes, September 19, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - District 8 Council Meeting Minutes, October 2, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - District 8 Council Meeting Minutes, April 15, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - District 8 Council Meeting Minutes, October 1944 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - District 8 Council Meeting Minutes, January 20, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - District 8 Council Meeting Minutes, March 24, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - District 8 Council Meeting Minutes, August 4, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - District 8 Council Meeting Minutes, October 6, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - District 8 Council Meeting Minutes, March 30 - October 5, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - District 8 Council Meeting Minutes, October 5, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - District 8 Council Meeting Minutes, March 29 - July 19, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - District 8 Council Meeting Minutes, October 4, 1947 - June 12, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - District 8 Council Meeting Minutes, September 25, 1948 - December 11, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - District 8 Council Meeting Minutes, March 24, 1950 - March 29, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - District 8 Council Meeting Minutes, March 29, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - District 8 Council Meeting Minutes, October 24, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - District 8 Council Meeting Minutes (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - District 8 Council Resolutions, September 24, 1939 - April 1941 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Resolution Regarding Organization, September 24, 1939; 1.
    - Resolution Regarding Foreign Policy, September 24, 1939; 2.
    - Resolution Regarding Foreign Policy Education, September 24, 1939; 3.
    - Resolution Regarding Women, Century Fur and Leather Workers Strike, Factionalism, Wages, Organization, Conscription and Recreation, September 21, 1940; 4.
    - Resolution Regarding Ford Organization, April 1941; 5.
    - Resolution Regarding United Mine Workers of America, April 1941; 6.
    - Resolution Regarding Wages, April 1941; 7.
    - Resolution Regarding International Harvester Strike, April 1941; 8.
    - Resolution Regarding Wages, April 1941; 9.
  - District 8 Council Resolutions, October 2, 1943 - August 4, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Resolution Regarding Taxes, Political Action, Labor Unity, Military Personnel, Womens Bureau and No-Strike Policy, October 2, 1943; 1.
    - Resolution Regarding Wages and Reconversion, August 4, 1945; 2.
    - Resolution Regarding Social Security, August 4, 1945; 3.
    - Resolution Regarding Smith Connally Act, August 4, 1945; 4.
    - Resolution Regarding Unemployment Compensation, August 4, 1945; 5.
    - Resolution Regarding War Criminals, August 4, 1945; 6.
    - Resolution Regarding UE News and Veterans, August 4, 1945; 7.
    - Resolution Regarding Racism, August 4, 1945; 8.
    - Resolution Regarding Severance Pay, August 4, 1945; 9.
    - Resolution Regarding Military Personnel, August 4, 1945; 10.
    - Resolution Regarding Ball-Hatch Burton Bill, August 4, 1945; 11.
    - Resolution Regarding Suffrage, August 4, 1945; 12.
    - Resolution Regarding British Labor Party, August 4, 1945; 13.
    - Resolution Regarding Officers, August 4, 1945; 14.
    - Resolution Regarding Poll Tax, August 4, 1945; 15.
    - Resolution Regarding Small Business, August 4, 1945; 16.
  - District 8 Council Resolutions, August 4, 1945 - March 20, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Resolution Regarding Women, August 4, 1945; 1.
    - Resolution Regarding Conscription, August 4, 1945; 2.
    - Resolution Regarding Education, August 4, 1945; 3.
    - Resolution Regarding Colonies, August 4, 1945; 4.
    - Resolution Regarding World Trade Union Congress, August 4, 1945; 5.
    - Resolution Regarding Veterans and Housing, August 4, 1945; 6.
    - Resolution Regarding Missouri Valley Authority, August 4, 1945; 7.
    - Resolution Regarding Housing, August 4, 1945; 8.
    - Resolution Regarding Government Factors, August 4, 1945; 9.
    - Resolution Regarding Spain and Argentina, August 4, 1945; 10.
    - Resolution Regarding Conversion, August 4, 1945; 11.
    - Resolution Regarding Minimum Contract Standards, October 5, 1946; 12.
    - Resolution Regarding Mario Russo, October 5, 1946; 13.
    - Resolution Regarding Newspapers, October 5, 1946; 14.
    - Resolution Regarding Political Action Committee, October 5, 1946; 15.
    - Resolution Regarding Political Action, October 5, 1946; 16.
    - Resolution Regarding Incentive, October 5, 1946; 17.
    - Resolution Regarding Spain and Argentina, October 5, 1946; 18.
    - Resolution Regarding Sidney Hillman, October 5, 1946; 19.
    - Resolution Regarding Strike, October 5, 1946; 20.
    - Resolution Regarding Legislation, October 5, 1946; 21.
    - Resolution Regarding UE Officers and Political Action, March 20, 1948; 22.
    - Resolution Regarding Political Action, March 20, 1948; 23.
  - District 8 Council Resolutions, October 24, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Resolution Regarding Taxation, October 24, 1953; 1.
    - Resolution Regarding Labor Unity, October 24, 1953; 2.
    - Resolution Regarding Political Action, October 24, 1953; 3.
    - Resolution Regarding Farmer Labor Unity, October 24, 1953; 4.
    - Resolution Regarding Matles-Emspak Defense Case, October 24, 1953; 5.
    - Resolution Regarding Union Policy, October 24, 1953; 6.
    - Resolution Regarding Organization, October 24, 1953; 7.
    - Resolution Regarding Hours, October 24, 1953; 8.
    - Resolution Regarding Publicity and Education, October 24, 1953; 9.
    - Resolution Regarding Social Security, October 24, 1953; 10.
  - District 8 William Sentner Incoming Correspondence, April 26, 1943 - July 8, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Janet Barish Regarding Finances, April 26, 1943; 1.
    - Barish Regarding Finances, June 30, 1943; 2.
    - Barish Regarding Finances, October 1, 1943; 3.
    - Barish Regarding Finances, December 21, 1943; 4.
    - Barish Regarding Finances, April 19, 1944; 5.
    - Barish Regarding Finances, July 3, 1944; 6.
    - Barish Regarding Finances, October 17, 1944; 7.
    - Barish Regarding Finances, February 16, 1945; 8.
    - Barish Regarding Finances, April 5, 1945; 9.
    - Barish Regarding Finances, August 23, 1945; 10.
    - Barish Regarding Finances, September 11, 1945; 11.
    - Barish Regarding Finances, December 20, 1945; 12.
    - Barish Regarding Finances, March 7, 1946; 13.
    - Barish Regarding Supplies, January 20, 1948; 14.
    - Barish Regarding Staff Finances, February 17, 1948; 15.
    - Barish Regarding Finances, March 2, 1948; 16.
    - Barish Regarding Finances, May 20, 1948; 17.
    - Barish Regarding Finances, July 8, 1948; 18.
    - David Berenstein Regarding Political Action, May 4, 1945; 19.
    - Carl Brant Regarding Staff Members, June 22, 1944; 20.
    - Neil Brant Regarding Workers Compensation Board, International Association of Machinists and U.S. Cartridge, March 17, 1942; 21.
    - Neil Brant Regarding Workers Compensation Board, May 4, 1943; 22.
    - John Burns Regarding Factoinalism and Local 1102 International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, July 10, 1946; 23.
  - District 8 William Sentner Incoming Correspondence, January 20, 1937 - April 26, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Bill Cahn Regarding Factionalism and UE News, April 19, 1948; 1.
    - Cahn Regarding Publicity, April 26, 1948; 2.
    - James Carey Regarding Factionalism, November 25, 1940; 3.
    - Carey Regarding Factionalism, December 5, 1940; 4.
    - Jack Cassidy Regarding Lincoln Western Electric Organization, December 12, 1945; 5.
    - James Clark Regarding Factionalism, Local 1102 and African-American Workers, June 29, 1945; 6.
    - John Cochran Regarding Dies Committee, March 5, 1942; 7.
    - Phillip Connelly Regarding Local 1421 and Factionalism, April 20, 1944; 8.
    - Frank Cronin Regarding Lincoln Western Electric Organization, February 5, 1945; 9.
    - Ernest DeMaio Regarding Cedar Rapids Collins Radio Organization, July 21, 1945; 10.
    - DeMaio Regarding Staff Members, December 31, 1942; 11.
    - Joseph Dermody Regarding Staff Members, August 24, 1945; 12.
    - Dermody Regarding Benton Edison GE Organization and United Mine Workers of America with October 17, 1945, Memo, October 22, 1945; 13.
    - George Dodson Regarding Factionalism and Philadelphia Organization, January 28, 1942; 14.
    - Lyle Dowling Regarding World War II, January 6, 1942; 15.
    - Dowling Regarding Taxation, undated; 16.
    - John Driy Regarding Emerson American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, February 25, 1942; 17.
    - Buford Eastman Regarding Lennox Furnace Organization and Wages, February 9, 1942; 18.
    - Bill Elconin Regarding Los Angeles Organization, December 8, 1941; 19.
  - District 8 William Sentner Incoming Correspondence, January 20, 1937 - May 20, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Local 1117, January 20, 1937; 1.
    - Emspak Regarding Dues and Local 1104, December 23, 1937; 2.
    - Emspak Regarding Unemployment, Dues and Local 1104, January 5, 1938; 3.
    - Emspak Regarding Century and Wages, January 21, 1938; 4.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, January 24, 1938; 5.
    - Emspak Regarding Factionalism, January 28, 1938; 6.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, February 5, 1938; 7.
    - Emspak Regarding Merger of Locals 808 and 1117, Local 1102 and Firings, February 5, 1938; 8.
    - Emspak Regarding Carey Visit, February 9, 1938; 9.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Local 1117, February 19, 1938; 10.
    - Emspak Regarding Address, February 24, 1938; 11.
    - Emspak Regarding Supplies, August 12, 1940; 12.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, November 14, 1940; 13.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, December 5, 1940; 14.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, January 2, 1941; 15.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and St. Louis Strike, January 13, 1941; 16.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Local 1103 Century Strike, January 21, 1941; 17.
    - Emspak Regarding Maytag, January 22, 1941; 18.
    - Emspak Regarding Supplies, January 29, 1941; 19.
    - Emspak Regarding Supplies and Finances, February 4, 1941; 20.
    - Emspak Regarding UE News, February 7, 1941; 21.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 1108 Century Strike, February 7, 1941; 22.
    - Emspak Regarding General Executive Board Meeting, February 17, 1941; 23.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, March 11, 1941; 24.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, April 2, 1941; 25.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, April 9, 1941; 26.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, April 10, 1941; 27.
    - Emspak Regarding UE News, April 18, 1941; 28.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, April 19, 1941; 29.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, April 23, 1941; 30.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, April 29, 1941; 31.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, May 6, 1941; 32.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, May 14, 1941; 33.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, May 20, 1941; 34.
  - District 8 William Sentner Incoming Correspondence, May 27 - September 29, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, May 27, 1941; 1.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, June 23, 1941; 2.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, June 9, 1941; 3.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, June 16, 1941; 4.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, June 23, 1941; 5.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, July 21, 1941; 6.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, August 4, 1941; 7.
    - Emspak Regarding Evansville American Bosch Organization, August 8, 1941; 8.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, August 9, 1941; 9.
    - Emspak Regarding General Executive Board Meeting, August 25, 1941; 10.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, September 5, 1941; 11.
    - Emspak Regarding Mid-West Emergency Conference, September 29, 1941; 12.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, September 29, 1941; 13.
  - District 8 William Sentner Incoming Correspondence, October 6, 1941 - April 15, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, October 6, 1941; 1.
    - Emspak Regarding Washing Machine Industry Organization, October 16, 1941; 2.
    - Emspak Regarding Dues, October 16, 1941; 3.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, October 21, 1941; 4.
    - Emspak Regarding Russ Nixon, October 24, 1941; 5.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, November 17, 1941; 6.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, November 28, 1941; 7.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, December 1, 1941; 8.
    - Emspak Regarding Arms Organization, December 8, 1941; 9.
    - Emspak Regarding Benjamin Contract, January 8, 1942; 10.
    - Emspak Regarding Arms Organization, January 8, 1942; 11.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, January 9, 1942; 12.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 825, January 23, 1942; 13.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, January 26, 1942; 14.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, February 10, 1942; 15.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, February 18, 1942; 16.
    - Emspak Regarding Workers Compensation Board, February 18, 1942; 17.
    - Emspak Regarding Moline Implement Organization, March 2, 1942; 18-19.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, March 2, 1942; 20.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, March 9, 1942; 21.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 815 Organization, March 16, 1942; 22.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, March 19, 1942; 23.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, March 31, 1942; 24.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, April 6, 1942; 25.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, April 15, 1942; 26.
  - District 8 William Sentner Incoming Correspondence, April 21 - October 17, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, April 21, 1942; 1.
    - Emspak Regarding Midwest Emergency Conference and Congressional, April 23, 1942; 2.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, April 27, 1942; 3.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, April 29, 1942; 4.
    - Emspak Regarding Meetings, April 30, 1942; 5.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, May 4, 1942; 6.
    - Emspak Regarding Publicity, May 12, 1942; 7.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville Organization, May 15, 1942; 8.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, May 20, 1942; 9.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, May 25, 1942; 10.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, June 3, 1942; 11.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, June 8, 1942; 12.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, June 15, 1942; 13.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, June 18, 1942; 14.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, June 22, 1942; 15.
    - Emspak Regarding United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, June 23, 1942; 16.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, June 29, 1942; 17.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, July 6, 1942; 18.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, July 13, 1942; 19.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, July 20, 1942; 20.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, September 9, 1942; 21.
    - Emspak Regarding Legislation, September 24, 1942; 22.
    - Emspak Regarding Brown-Wagner Resolution and Congress of Industrial Organizations, September 25, 1942; 23.
    - Emspak Regarding General Executive Board, Wages, AFL and Cairo, October 17, 1942; 24.
  - District 8 William Sentner Incoming Correspondence, October 19, 1942 - July 21, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Soviet-American Friendship Congress, October 19, 1942; 1.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, December 29, 1942; 2.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, February 17, 1943; 3.
    - Emspak Regarding Insurance and U.S. Cartridge, February 27, 1943; 4.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, March 1, 1943; 5.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 1102, March 25, 1943; 6.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, April 5, 1943; 7.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, April 12, 1943; 8.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, April 26, 1943; 9.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, May 4, 1943; 10.
    - Emspak Regarding General Executive Board, May 6, 1943; 11.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, May 10, 1943; 12.
    - Emspak Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations, May 10, 1943; 13.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, May 12, 1943; 14.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, May 17, 1943; 15.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, May 26, 1943; 16.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, June 1, 1943; 17.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, June 8, 1943; 18.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, June 21, 1943; 19.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, July 6, 1943; 20.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, July 12, 1943; 21.
    - Emspak Regarding Women's Conference and Small Arms Negotiations, July 14, 1943; 22.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, July 16, 1943; 23.
    - Emspak Regarding Evansville and Finances, July 21, 1943; 24.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, July 21, 1943; 25.
  - District 8 William Sentner Incoming Correspondence, August 4 - December 3, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, August 4, 1943; 1.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, August 9, 1943; 2.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, August 18, 1943; 3.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, August 26, 1943; 4-5.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, September 2, 1943; 6.
    - Emspak Regarding 1943 Convention and Local 1108, September 8, 1943; 7.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Evansville, September 22, 1943; 8.